Hey guys, welcome to another video, the another session.
So this session will be important for everyone who is going to real-time attacks in any
of the company or any of the organizations because you can't able to use any third-party
tools to do some attacks, where it will be easily catch up by antivirus softwares or
EDR softwares, EDR platform or EDR platform. So instead of that, you have another
option called as a law dash. So this is a very great different aviation mechanism.
So because the antivirus softwares, if there is a third-party application like third-party
malware, third-party installers, so they will be added their hash value in the antivirus
softwares or EDR side, so it will be detected as a static or dynamic detection, but
you can't able to do anything if it was detected, but you can use a law dash instead of
going for any other third-party application, because threat tactics and hackers, real-time
hackers and the real-world hackers, they will be using the law dash to do certain attacks
and multiple attacks. So Bias, I have handled a lot of incidents like more than 100 plus
incidents in experience and so whatever incidents which I am facing in 100 percent of
the incidents, the threat tactics are using the law dash for multiple attacks. So that
will be the more important. So this section will be more important for everyone to watch.
So if you have a good understanding about this session, so you can understand how the threat
tactic will operate and how the incident responders or threat-only story, if you are in a
SARC or EDR, any any positions you are in, you can easily investigate your threat or you can
easily go and attack the organization by evading the bypassing the antivirus softwares and
EDR platforms. So let's take a lot of minutes, let's go to the law. So law dash was an
example, full form of living of the land binary scripts and libraries. Okay, this is like
so our Windows machine already have a lot of lot of things like so if you go for
let me go to my C and let me go to the C Windows 32.
So the Microsoft content's lot of binaries and driver files and many, many, many executable
called as a system Donald's. There is a lot of lot of things will be 100 of the machines.
So if we search the rendial 32.exe, so you can find, this was not pulled by any of the third
party application I didn't download or this rendial 32.exe and put it in the system that you do.
So instead of when you are installing the operating system, so it will be get automatically
instructed, it will be come with the Windows operating system. So at the better point,
we do one thing. So when I installed my operating system, the rendial 32 and a lot of lot of
log-ins are there, it will be get automatically instead of the machine, you don't need to
download it manually and you go to pull it in the machine. So we are using this kind of executable,
this kind of system internals, this kind of law there, literally, to do further attacks,
okay, to do post-expirations, activities, okay. So the real time, the attackers are a real world
hack of, they will be late, they will be 100% delay on the log-ins because they know the other
third party tools, if they download from any of the internet, it will be easily catch up by
EDR platform and antivirus platform. So we are completely using the log-in for that, okay,
living of the learns binaries and libraries, okay. So let's go to the living of the land
binaries page so you can see this is the project one of, you can go to the URL, log-based project
GitHub so it just hurts your log-ins in Google. I did not prepare any presentation here because
it's completely going to a practical, so presentations are literally based, but I will give all
the script, you say, how tested, which I have been executing in the, in this session, okay.
So let our first blog, that was abusing your NDL32.exe, let's get on to the NDLL32.exe,
so you can see the miter tactics here, so it was coming up with the two tactics in DFS and
another one tactics are here, you can check what the tactics is, so if you want,
if you want to let go for a, go for checking the tactics, so you can see the system binary,
proxy execution, we are a DLS that was a system binary, the NDL32.exe, it will be already
present in set of machines for DLS and the DLS function, so it was saying the payload will be
a DLS payload will be get executed via NDL32.exe with the DLS name and the DLS functions, okay.
So let's return to the DLS32.exe, so this application, this application will teach you how
the threat tactics will use the DLS, use the law desk to do a further attacks to do a post-exploration
activities in the machine, so if first thing, you can say we can, we previously seen this
aren't executing the DLS using their NDL32.exe, so you can see here the threat tactics,
most of the time they will be using the NDL32 for executing the DLS in set of machines,
so I already mentioned, so DLS, if you need to execute the DLS, you need to call the entry
point of the machine, right. So this is the all things X64 DLS and this is the entry points,
so you have to call the entry point of the machine, also you can execute the DLS from the SMB shares,
if you have a remote share or remote access share, so you can execute the DLS from remotely by
calling the entry point, okay. So also you have some other options to download from a remote
of support, that is downloaded from a remote-upset and etc, okay. So you have also other
techniques that can be followed, but most of the time it will be go for data executions,
stuff like that, okay. So if you want to research more, you can use the, you can use the
website so you can research those things, but I am going with executing a DLS basically,
the NDL32.exe was sponsored for executing a DLS stuffs and all,
let's go to our view machines, so we already created a DLS file,
which we have that was named as a hello dot DLL. Let's execute this, we know the entry
point of the LLD as the, see it's previously, let's execute the PBR, if you want to see.
So we have created the DLL with only one function, right, the REN box, REN message box,
something, let's check that and we will do the task, so let's load the DLL. So hello,
let's start DLL, let's load it, so we previously seen each and everything here, let's go to the
export, so you can see there is only one function, REN message box. So let's execute, let's execute
the REN message box by calling the entry point, so this is the DLL function which we have
programmed before, so let's call this REN DLL32.exe, so let's, let's give the DLL here,
hello, let's start DLL, you have to give a comma and you can, you can directly execute that,
so now you can see the, DLL has been executed, hello from DLL, right,
so instead of placing the hello from DLL, the threat attacker will place the shell codes
are any malicious code instead of, instead of hello from DLL and they will execute in the,
instead of machine, okay, so that was the real world scenario, how the DLL will be,
get executed in the system, it was used to build on a lot of malware, it's not a lot of threat
types of, DLL was used by, a lot of threat types, a lot of incidents, okay, so I hope you have
clear understanding about the REN DLL32.exe, we will hop off the CD and we will continue our
discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye bye.